innokin.com 2019-10-01

# PRIVACY POLICY – A Better Vape Experience

Innokin.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the Innokin.com website and services. This privacy policy covers the website and activities of Innokin.com.

This Privacy Policy describes how Innokin.com collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide. It also describes your choices regarding use of your personal information. The Innokin.com website is owned and operated by Innokin Technology Ltd.

Innokin is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives. Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our website and with our brand. Emails and information are collected in order to complete Support Services, Giveaways and more. Innokin.com will not share any personal information with any third party at any time, unless required by law.

Please be aware that Innokin.com sponsors, advertisers and partners or affiliates with co-branded modules or sections on Innokin.com may collect personally identifiable information about you while on our website. The information practices of those parties are not covered by this privacy statement. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by us.

Innokin.com users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas and forums, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. To request removal of your personal information from our website, or forum, contact us at info@innokin.com.

In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Innokin.com does not collect personally identifying information about any individual website user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, we may ask you for information, such as your e-mail address when you register to become a member of Innokin.com. You may also provide information to Innokin.com in other contexts, including, for example, on your member profile page and public profile URL or to enter into a giveaways or promotion.

We and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base. A cookie is a small data file that is written to your computer’s hard drive by your web browser. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user identification code, that a website will use to track the pages and number of times you have visited.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, choose to accept cookies only from certain websites or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our website, you may not be able to use certain features of the site.

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our website and brand. From time to time we may provide e-mails highlighting new features, promotions or contests on the website to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to send such communications as part of their user profile. If you do not wish to receive emails you may unsubscribe from the list at any time.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in giveaways or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you, such as your name and e-mail. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We use this personally identifiable information to notify contest winners and award prizes.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

You can log in to our site using sign-in services that bridge your social media login information with Innokin.com. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to prefill our sign up form. These services give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Our website includes social media features, widgets and/or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features are small content modules that users can embed on sites and may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, or set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

We offer widgets that are hosted on Innokin.com. Use of the Innokin.com widgets is subject to the Innokin.com terms of use but downloading or embedding these widgets on other websites is not covered by this privacy statement.

Individuals under 18/21 (legal smoking age) should not use Innokin products or the Innokin Website. Do not send any information about yourself to us–including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from those under the age of 18/21. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a young person under the age of 18/21 we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at info@innokin.com
